{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.401Z","__v":0,"assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","dirty":true,"needForAction":{"work":8,"leisure":9,"stresstypus":2,"handling":9},"owner":"539853d7499b2ec3fb001808","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.616Z","answers":[{"created":"2014-06-11T13:04:47.683Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000dd","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":50,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00185e"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:04:48.970Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000dc","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":-50,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00185d"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:04:50.108Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000db","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":50,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00185c"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:04:53.196Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000da","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":-72,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00185b"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:04:53.436Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d9","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00185a"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:04:57.181Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d8","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":77,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001859"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:00.310Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d7","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":31,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001858"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:02.474Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d6","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":-78,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001857"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:06.705Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d5","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":21,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001856"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:10.235Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.395Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d4","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":28,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001855"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:11.163Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d3","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001854"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:14.731Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d1","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":-50,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001853"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:15.339Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000d0","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001852"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:16.693Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000cf","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001851"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:19.833Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000ce","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":77,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001850"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:23.444Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000cc","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":25,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00184f"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:25.335Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000cb","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":73,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00184e"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:27.928Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000ca","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":75,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00184d"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:30.268Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c9","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":19,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00184c"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:30.598Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c8","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00184b"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:34.200Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c6","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":-81,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb00184a"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:35.002Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c5","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001849"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:35.764Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c4","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001848"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:37.618Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c3","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":-50,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001847"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:39.707Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c2","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":24,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001846"},{"created":"2014-06-11T13:05:40.304Z","updated":"2014-06-11T13:05:47.396Z","question":"5278c51a6166f2de240000c1","assessment":"525faf0ac558d40000000005","answer":0,"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001845"}],"id":"5398542b499b2ec3fb001844"}